Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
（佳乃(よしの)）ヤーッ！
（切る音）
Mazu ore ga run dat
Hashirimawatte yatsura o gun shot
（梶浦(かじうら)）ウワッ… アアッ！
Brand new sound sou still survival
Here come the sound boy kono sekai ni ikiro
（計(けい)たち）あっ…
Chiryoku tairyoku to un ga mau ze! Flow
Fukuranda ataman naka wa zakkubaran nan da
Savannah de Banna ni wanpan
Kantan knockout kan kan kan
One time for your mind ikinuke
Around the world
Tsukimatou no sa itsu no itami mo
Kedakai kami no mawari mo ima karimono
Makareta tane mo hana sakeba dare no
Ikite uchikomu shinnen no ya o more more more
Ikisaki ni yasuragi wa nai
Tachi na sa don't give up the fight
Ima sou kono shunkan mo die die die
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
（室戸(むろと)）ハハッ… うれしい！
Simply delightful!
Let's All Go Back Alive
Wow...
Check it out... This is awesome!
（室戸）
すっげえな これ　すげえよ
Huh? Really?
えっ？ ホント？
Hey, he said we can use these!
ねえ 使っていいってさ これ
Huh?
Come on, man, get it together, will ya?
It's not that bad.
（室戸）あ～あ…
（室戸）だらしないな そんな傷で
Sh... Shut up, you little fuck! I'll kill you!
（梶浦）う… うるせえ クソガキ！
殺すぞ アアッ…
SEXY COBORET
Paradise
Don't do anything stupid!
（古田(ふるた)）
バカなマネは やめるんだ！
SEXY COBORET
Paradise
Be quiet!
（斉藤(さいとう)）うるさい！ アア…
A person just died! How can you be so calm?
人が死んだんだぞ
よく平気でいられるな！
We are far from calm!
（古田）平気なわけないだろう！
（斉藤）ウソだ！
You're lying!
What you're saying sounds all fine and well,
（斉藤）もっともらしいことを
言っているけど―
but as far as you're concerned
this is all someone else's problem!
本当は他人ごとなんだ
"Talk him out of it"? Come on!
You're just on some sort of ego trip!
（斉藤）“説得”？
自分が満足したいだけでしょう？
Don't be ridiculous!
何を言う？
Then you should go by yourself!
You're just full of yourself, you egoist!
だったら １人で行けばいいんだ！
あんたは ただのエゴイストだ！
（古田）エゴイスト？ 私が？
Egoist? You mean, ME?
That's right! You're always imposing
your own ideas on others!
（斉藤）そうだ
あんた いつも自分の考えを
他人に押しつけているでしょう？
But I bet you really don't give
a damn about anyone else!
周りのことなんて
考えてないんじゃないですか？
All right...
（古田）分かった
You guys wait here.
（古田）
君たちは ここで待っていてくれ
I'll go by myself!
私１人で行ってくる
Now he's pissed.
（野崎(のざき)）
むくれちまった　どうする？
What do we do?
Kill them.
殺す！
フフッ… だろうな
That's what I thought.
How about you, Missy?
ねえちゃんは？
（みか）あっ… 私？
I, um...
Well, if everyone else is going...
みんなが行くなら…
How about you?
（野崎）あんたは？
（斉藤）フッ…
There's no way I'm going. This is ridiculous!
行くわけないでしょう
ばかばかしい
Are you sure about that?
（野崎）本当に それでいいのか？
（斉藤）えっ？ うん？
If they get us, they'll definitely
come after you next.
（野崎）俺たちが やられれば
次は間違いなく あんたの番だ
Maybe helping us for now is a better idea, huh?
（野崎）協力しといたほうが
いいんじゃないか？
Hinodedai Funeral Hall
ウウ…
（野崎）おい
Hey, stay with us, all right?
ウウ…
（野崎）離れんじゃねえぞ
（みか）ハァ ハァ ハァ…
ハハッ… よう！
What's up?
You little piece of shit! I'll kill you!
ガキ ぶっ殺す！
くそ これじゃ… あっ…
Damn it! At this rate...
（銃撃音）
（野崎）ウワッ！
I don't wanna do this...
I don't wanna do this anymore...
（斉藤）もうイヤだ もうイヤだ
（空撃ちの音）
（室戸）あれ？
Die!
（野崎）死ねー！
ウワッ！
Wait!
待ってくれ！
（野崎）なに？
What the...
I'm going to take him back with me!
So you can't shoot him!
（古田）この子は連れて帰る
撃っちゃいかん！
Stop talking nonsense!
Now get out of there quick!
バカなこと言ってんじゃねえ！
早くどけ！
No!
（古田）
ダメだ！ 彼は まだ未成年だ
He's still a minor!
If we just speak to him the right way,
he ought to understand!
ちゃんと話してあげれば
分かってくれるはずだ
Mr. Muroto!
室戸君！
What you're doing is wrong!
君の やっていることは
いけないことだ
You're only being used by that man!
君は あの男にダマされているんだ
Come on now, give me the gun.
（古田）さあ 銃をよこしなさい
Can I trust you?
（室戸）信じていいんですか？
（古田）もちろんだ
Of course you can.
I think you'll find I'm not like other adults.
私は
ほかの大人たちとは違うつもりだ
さあ
Come on now.
So you understand.
（古田）分かってくれたんだね
Yes.
Thank you, Sir...
ありがとう おじさん
面白かったよ
That was fun.
（みか・計）ウワッ！
（梶浦）ウワッ…
（爆発音）
ウワーッ！
Hajime! Shoot! Shoot!
（梶浦）一(はじめ)！ 撃て 撃て！
Damn! That little shit!
（梶浦）くそ！ あのガキ！
（計）あいつ！
That bastard!
Nozaki!
（みか）野崎君！
（計）あっ…
Nozaki!
（計）野崎！
（野崎）ウッ…
Nozaki!
Are you okay?
（みか）大丈夫？ 野崎君
（野崎）まあ… なんとかな
Yeah, barely...
But what happened to Saito?
それより 斉藤は どうなった？
（計）あっ…
（みか）斉藤さん…
Mr. Saito?
NO!
（みか）イヤーッ！
イヤ！
イヤ… イヤー…
It's my fault...
（古田）私のせいだ…
It's all my fault...
（古田）全て私のせいだ
All I do is preach to others, as if
I know what I'm talking about,
私は…
偉そうに説教ばかりしていて
何の役にも立っていない
but I'm absolutely useless...
I let him die...
彼を死なせたのは私だ
We can't let him keep killing people!
これ以上 彼に
人殺しをさせるわけにはいかない
Please take care of the rest.
（古田）あとを頼むよ
（みか）待ってください
Please wait!
I'm coming, too.
（みか）私も行きます
（古田）えっ？
Huh?
（みか）いいでしょう？
It's okay, isn't it?
Be careful.
気をつけろよ
Let's go, Mr. Furuta.
（みか）行こう 古田さん
Are you sure?
（古田）いいのかい？
I'm already dead...
（みか）
どうせ １度死んでるんだから…
Nothing can surprise me now.
もう何が起こっても驚かないわ
後悔は したくないの
I don't want to regret it later.
That girl's got a lot of guts.
気合い入った ねえちゃんだぜ
俺 ホレちゃいそう
I think I'm in love.
Did you guys have a girl like
that before, too?
前回もいたか？ ああいうの
Yeah, we did.
ああ いたよ
And Mika said if it wasn't for her,
その人がいなけりゃ―
she'd never have been able
to buy that book, Labyrinth.
あの子は 「迷宮」って本
買えなかったんだってさ
Negative chain reaction, huh?
（野崎）負の連鎖ってやつか
I'm going to fuck Kajiura up!
梶浦 つぶしに行くぜ！
Damn. That bastard, Hajime...
（梶浦）くそ…
はじめの野郎 ふざけやがって
Fuck with me, will he?
I'm gonna kill him!
ぶっ殺してやる！
Where the hell did they find those guns anyway?
（野崎）
しかし あいつら あの銃 どこで？
It's Gantz. I know Gantz gave
them those weapons!
（計）ガンツだ
ヤツが用意したに決まってる
What the hell does Gantz want?
（野崎）何がしてえんだよ？
そのガンツっての
I think I will go by myself after all.
（古田）やはり １人で行きます
You should stay with them...
君は彼らと一緒に…
（みか）私…
I...
I was stabbed to death by a stalker...
ストーカーに刺し殺されたんです
（古田）えっ？
What?
何にもできずに殺されちゃって…
I was dead before I could do anything about it...
It's so frustrating...
それが悔しくて
I should've fought back harder then!
もっと もっと
戦わないとダメだったのよ
（みか）だから…
So...
梶浦！ あっ…
Kajiura!
Hey, so what took you so long, you little fuck?
（梶浦）よう
遅かったじゃねえか クソガキ
C'mon, sit down and have a drink.
とりあえず１杯 やんなよ
ハハッ… そっか
Oh yeah, you kids are still
too young to drink, huh?
お前(めえ)ら 未成年だから飲めねえか
Have some sushi then.
じゃ 寿司(すし)食え 寿司
There must be a few that
don't have any wasabi in 'em.
ワサビ抜きとかも
あんじゃねえのか？ フフッ…
What the hell is going on?
どうなってんだ？
（室戸）ハハハハッ… バ～カ 梶浦
That dumb ass Kajiura...
I hope he got killed by the Kurono Alien.
玄野(くろの)星人に ぶっ殺されろよ
After that I'll take out the ones
who are left one by one.
そのあとで 残りのヤツら
１人ずつ殺してやるぜ
Huh? I thought I had more of these...
Where did they go?
あれ？ これ もっとあったよな
どこ行った？
Mr. Muroto!
（古田）室戸君！
（室戸）なっ…
Looks like that Gantz thing
left us some amazing stuff here.
ガンツってやつ すげえの
置いといてくれたみてえだぜ
If you eat these, you won't feel any pain.
これ食やぁ
痛みなんか感じなくなる
I'm great right now.
すっげえいい気分だ
C'mon, let's sing a song
or something. Let's party!
まあ 歌でも歌って
パ～ッと やろうや
Is what Kurono said true?
（古田）玄野君の言ってたこと
本当だったのか？
Huh? You mean about the homeless guy?
（室戸）
えっ？ ホームレスのこと？
Yeah, it was.
そうだよ
梶浦より いっぱい殺したかな
Maybe I killed even more of them than Kajiura.
What's going on in your head anyway?!
（古田）
君は 一体 何を考えてるんだ？
（室戸）ハハハッ… あのさ
Hey, will you stop preaching to me?
It's really getting on my nerves.
説教とか やめてくれる？
ウザイんだよね
I'm not preaching to you!
（古田）説教ではない！
（室戸）
フッ… なに？ それ　本気？
What's that?
Are you serious?
（古田）君は 私や みんなをダマし
You deceived me and everybody else.
On top of that, you killed Yoshino and Saito...
佳乃さんと斉藤さんまで…
（室戸）ウッ… な… 何だよ？
What... What do you want?
It's... It's all you adults' fault!
（室戸）大人が…
大人が悪いんじゃないか！
Stop blaming others!
（古田）人のせいにするな！
That's enough!
（古田）もういい
こんな…
Enough of this meaningless cycle of violence!
こんな無意味な負の連鎖は私が…
I'm going to... I'm going to...
私が…
It's the beginning of a brand new day
A day filled with hope
This son of a bitch...
こいつ…
だから まともじゃねえんだって
I told you, they're off the edge.
A day filled with hope
Open your heart to happiness
Kill each other some more, please.
And look up at the big, blue sky
Listen to the voice on the radio
And fill your lungs
With the fragrant air
Come on
One!
Two!
Three!
Shit...
（計）あっ… の… 野崎…
No... Nozaki...
Nozaki!
あっ… 野崎！
（野崎）ウウッ…
ウッ… そっか…
Oh I get it...
You're the guy from that time...
お前 あんときの…
What? What are you talking about?
（計）何だ？ 何言ってる？
Kurono...
玄野 気をつけろ
Better be careful...
The sickest one here isn't Gantz...
いちばんヤバイのはガンツじゃねえ
It's... a human...
（野崎）人間 …だぜ
Nozaki!
野崎ーっ！
アア… ふ… 古田さん…
Mr. Furuta!
Hey, old man.
（室戸）おら おっさん
Stay still, okay?
（室戸）おとなしくしてろよ
ピンが抜けたら頭吹っ飛ぶぜ
If the pin comes out,
it'll blow your head off.
（室戸）フフッ… 更に…
And...
（室戸）アア…
（みか）や… やめて…
（室戸）フフフッ…
（みか）やめて…
Stop... Stop it...
Nozaki...
野崎…
You son of a bitch!
てめえ…
てめえ！
（梶浦）フフッ…
いいもん見せてやろうか？
Wanna see something cool?
Tada!
（梶浦）ジャ～ン
Pretty cool, huh?
いいだろう？ これ
一緒に吹っ飛ぼうぜ
Let's get blown away together!
Your eyes... look just like Hajime's
and they're pissing me off.
てめえの その目な…
はじめに そっくりで
ムカつくんだよ
ＯＫ
Okay!
He's out of his mind.
（梶浦）あいつは まともじゃねえ
All he ever thinks about is killing people.
四六時中
人殺すことばっか考えてんのよ
ねえ
Hey, do you want to do something fun?
（室戸）いいことしようか
Don't move. If you do,
his head will go "ka-boom!"
動くなよ
動くと おっさんの頭 バ～ンだぜ
I said, "Don't move"!
（室戸）動くなっつってんだろう！
ハハハハッ…
I'm much nicer than Kajiura because
I don't kill you right away.
（室戸）あの梶浦に比べれば
僕なんか かわいいもんですよ
だって すぐには殺さないから
And Kajiura's killed so many people, all women.
あいつさ…
ムチャクチャいっぱい殺してるわけ
それも女ばっか
I don't really have any preferences like that.
僕は そういうこだわり ないから
I'm a lot nicer than Hajime.
（梶浦）はじめに比べりゃ
俺なんか かわいいもんよ
女しか殺さねえしな
I only kill women.
Up until today I've never actually killed a man.
男ぶっ殺したのは
今日が初めてなんだよ
（野崎）気をつけろ
Better be careful...
いちばんヤバイのは人間だぜ
The sickest one here is...
a human...
Kato was so weak.
加藤(かとう)君 弱かったよ
（計）なに？
What?!
（千手観音）
僕に やられちゃった フフフッ…
I killed him.
I knew you did it...
（計）やっぱり やったんだな
（計）ハァ ハァ ハァ…
You killed Kato, didn't you?!
てめえが加藤をやったんだな！
You guys die because you try to beat Gantz.
（千手観音）君たちはさ ガンツに
勝とうなんて思うから死ぬんだよ
This is the end so you should just accept it.
ただの終わりなんだから
すんなり受け入れればいいのにさ
Kato...
（計）加藤…
I hope you're watching!
見てろよ 加藤！
こんなのって…
How could you...
こんなのって！
How could you do this!?
（室戸）ウウッ… 痛(いて)え…
It hurts!
痛えよ！
You're here to die?
死にに来たか？
Let's all go back alive!
（加藤）みんなで生きて帰ろう
You know, I'm trying hard to be like you, Kei.
（加藤）俺 計ちゃんみたいに
なろうって頑張ってんだよね
帰ろう みんなで
Let's go back... together... alive...
生きて
You're right... KATO!
（計）そうだよな
加藤！
ウワーッ！
Just like she told me...
（みか）
あの人が言ってたとおりなんだ
Words aren't enough on their own.
言葉で言ってるだけじゃ…
In the end, I have to use my own
strength and FIGHT!
最後は
自分の力で戦わないとダメなんだ
（梶浦）ウワッ！
Kato...
（計）加藤 生きて帰ろうぜ！
Let's go back alive! All right?
なあっ！
Hajimari wa dare demo junshin muku na baby
Nigai mi kajitte mo kujikecha
dame yo walk straight
Satta koto da kedo ame no naka
zukizuki itamu yo
I'm lonely as floating ice
Yaseta yubi ni kiss o shite
Naita anata o omoidasu yo
Kore de owari da to shite mo
Saigo no kiss wa wasurenai yo
Wasurenai yo
Kare no kiss o wasurenai yo
You bastard... Gantz...
（計）てめえ… ガンツ
ガンツ… ガンツ ガンツ
Gantz...
Gantz... Gantz!
Gantz, Gantz, Gantz!
ガンツ ガンツ ガンツ！
You son of a bitch, Gantz!
てめえ この野郎！ ガンツー！
Final episode, "Please Live"
最終回 “生きてくれ”